Nooo!
!لـ-لا
I'm falling! I'm falling!
!سأسقط! سأسقط
I'm falling!
!سأسقط
Alright! We've landed!
!حسنًا، وصلنا
Boy, I'm exhausted.
تعبت حقًا
Don't "we've landed" me! I thought I was going to die!
!لا تقل "وصلنا" ببساطة هكذا !اعتقدت أنّي سأموت
What else could we have done?!
!لم يكن لديّ خيار آخر
You're the one who said we couldn't use the elevator or else they would find us!
أنتِ من قال أنّ لا ينبغي علينا استخدام المصعد
That doesn't mean you had to jump off!
!رغم ذلك، لا داعي لأن تقفز من الأعلى
You're not that square-nosed shipwright!
!لسنا مثل السفان مربّع الأنف ذاك
I... I'm sorry.
آ-آسف
Well, fine. At least it got us down.
ولكن لا بأس بما أنّنا نزلنا
If it's fine, then don't hit me!
!لا تضربيني إن لم يوجد بأس
But... this seems pretty bad.
ولكن... قد يكون هذا سيّئًا قليلًا
Bad? What's bad?
سيّئ؟ ما السيّئ؟
The geography and weather of this island.
تضاريس وطقس هذه الجزيرة
With this much wind blowing, if the atmospheric pressure drops,
مع هبوب هذا القدر من الرياح فإن انخفض ضغط الغلاف الجوّي
a typhoon might come through tonight.
فقد يمرّ إعصار من هنا هذه الليلة
This town is called the City of Water.
تدعى هذه البلدة بمدينة الماء
In other words, it's prone to suffering flood damage.
بمعنى آخر، تمتلك نقطة ضعف قد تؤدي بسهولة لتكبّد أضرار فيضانات
So? What about it?
وما بذلك؟
Well, it bothers me a little, so I'll look into it later.
في الواقع... هذا يثير فضولي قليلًا لذا سأتحقق من الأمر لاحقًا
Anyway, let's get back to the inn.
على أيّ حال، لنرجع إلى النُزل الآن
Following the Aqua Laguna warning issued for the entire island,
تبعًا لتحذير أكوا لاغونا الصادر للجزيرة بأكملها
all the shipbuilding factories and docks on Shipyard Island will be opened as evacuation centers.
جميع مواني وأحواض السفانة في جزيرة السفانة
We expect large crowds, so please evacuate as soon as possible.
يُتوقع وجود أعداد كبيرة لذا الرجاء الإخلاء باكرًا
Additionally, since Dock One is currently in a dangerous state...
علاوة على ذلك، بما أنّ الحوض الأوّل ...في وضع خطر حاليًا
Okay, I'll put the iron plate on.
حسنًا، سأضع اللوح الحديدي
You have everything you need?
ألم تنسوا شيئًا؟
Yes, we do. Let's evacuate to the shipyard.
لا، لنخلِ إلى حوض السفانة
Well, hold on a bit. I'd better fill the gap good with rope.
تمهلوا قليلًا. عليّ أن أملأ الفتحات بالقنب
If our house gets flooded, everything will be ruined.
إن غمر الماء منزلنا فسيفسد كلّ ما فيه
Hey, the wind is starting to get strong! Get ready for waves soon!
!بدأت الرياح تهبّ بقوّة !استعدوا للأمواج قريبًا
Guys! If we take too long, assassin pirates will show up!
يا جماعة، إن تباطأتم، فإنّ القراصنة !القتلة سيظهرون هذه المرة أيضًا
That's scary!
!هذا مخيف
Where'd he disappear to?!
!إلى أين اختفى؟
I'm pretty sure he came this way.
أنا متأكد أنّه أتى إلى هنا
He should still be around!
!ينبغي أن يكون قريبًا
Okay, you guys go look over there.
حسنًا، اذهبوا للبحث هناك
Got it!
!مفهوم
What the hell is going on?
ماذا يجري؟
Why're they chasing me? I don't get it!
!لماذا أُلاحق؟ لا أدري ما الذي يجري
So this is the reason!
!هذا سبب لحاقهم لي إذًا
We're a crew of assassins?
مرتكبي عملية اغتيال؟
What a pain. Now I can't even go back to the inn.
يا إلهي... لا أستطيع الرجوع إلى النُزل هكذا
Ah... Who's over there?!
!من الذي هناك؟
Over here! I found someone suspicious!
!هنا! وجدت شخصًا مشبوهًا هنا
Are you sure, innkeeper?
هل أنت متأكّد يا صاحب النُزل؟
Yes. Those pirates have been staying at my inn since last night.
نعم. بقى أولئك القراصنة هنا منذ الليلة الماضية
They were just here...
كانوا هنا قبل قليل فحسب
They were here?!
!كانوا هنا؟
Yes!
نعم. بما أنّهم لا يزالون يملكون أغراضًا كثيرة في غرفتهم
Okay, then! You guys, stay here.
حسنًا. أنتم ابقوا هنا
The rest of us will start searching the area!
!فليرافقني البقية للبحث في هذه المنطقة
Listen, make sure you leave no stone unturned to find them!
!اسمعوا، لا تدعوا حجرًا إلّا وبحثتم تحته لإيجادهم
– Yeah!
!أجل
Hey, there's no one here!
!لا يوجد أحد
Is this really their ship?
أهذه سفينتهم حقًا؟
There's no mistake about it! Look!
!لا شكّ بذلك. انظر
That's the Straw Hat Pirates' flag.
هذا علم قراصنة طاقم قبعة القش
I bet they've already abandoned it.
لا بدّ وأنّهم تخلوا عنها
This ship is all beat up.
إنّها بحالة يرثى لها
So? Did you find them?
إذًا؟ أَوجدتموهم؟
No, they aren't here!
!لا، ليسوا هنا
There isn't much left inside. They must've abandoned ship.
بما أنّ لم يكن هناك الكثير على متن السفينة، فلا بدّ وأنّهم تخلوا عنها
Let's look elsewhere.
لنبحث في مكان آخر
Who were they?
من كانوا؟
Is something happening in town?
أيحدث شيء في المدينة؟
Did you find them?
هل وجدتهم؟
No.
لا
Dammit! Where could they be...?
!سحقًا! أين هم؟
Hey, Luffy...
لوفي
Yeah? What's up, Nami?
ما الخطب يا نامي؟
Do you think everyone's okay?
أتعتقد أنّ الآخرين بخير؟
Craftsmen are everywhere in town.
الحرفيون في جميع أنحاء المدينة
I think Chopper and Sanji should be okay since their faces are still unknown.
لم يكتشفوا أمر تشوبر وسانجي-كن ...بعد، لذا أظنّهما بخير، ولكن
Let's hurry anyway!
!لنسرع على أيّ حال
Yeah.
أجل
The sea train is still in service...
...لا يزال القطار البحري تحت الصيانة
The afternoon train already left, but it seems there's still a night departure despite the weather.
يبدو أنّ قطار بعد الظهيرة غادر بالفعل
Bound for Enies Lobby at eleven tonight... The sea train is pretty impressive.
،يغادر في الساعة 11 مساءً إلى إنيس لوبي !يا له من قطار بحري مثير للإعجاب
Hey! Any information on the pirates?!
!أثمّة معلومات عن القراصنة؟
No. We've got nothing.
لا، أبدًا
If we can just capture one and squeeze 'em, they'll spill the beans on the rest.
إن أمسكنا واحدًا من أولئك الثلاثة الذين نعرف وجوههم وأجبرناهم على الكلام فسنتعرف على باقي الطاقم
Hurry, before the waves get too high!
!أسرعوا! قبل أن ترتفع الأمواج
I wonder if Robin got on the sea train.
أتعتقد أنّ روبين ركبت القطار؟
If she did, things can't get any worse.
ستصبح الأمور أفظع ما يمكن إن فعلت
Water Seven is already too big to handle...
حتّى ووتر سيفن وحدها شاسعة ...ولا نستطيع مواكبة الأمر
I wonder if I did something to upset her at the bookstore.
هل فعلتُ شيئًا أغضبها في المكتبة حقًا؟
You dummy. There's no way that's the case.
أيّها الغبي... هذا مستحيل
Oh, hey you.
أنت
Have you seen a pretty woman like her?
ألم ترَ هذه الجميلة في مكان ما؟
Oh... You mean the pretty woman who looked like that twenty years ago?
إنّها الجميلة التي تكبر هذه الصورة بعشرين سنة، أليست كذلك؟
If I had, I would've immediately told the newspaper or Galley-La.
كنت لأخبر إمّا شركة الصحيفة أو غاليلا على الفور لو فعلت
But to think she's an assassin...
،ولكنّي لم أتوقّع أن تكون قاتلة !يا لها من مفاجأة
Well, it's nice of you to help look for the culprits, but you should evacuate soon.
على أيّ حال، لا بأس بالبحث عن الجناة ولكن عليكما الإخلاء بسرعة
Aqua Laguna will swallow you otherwise.
وإلّا ستبتلعكما أكوا لاغونا
See ya.
إلى اللقاء
Things are going wrong for all of us.
...أصبحت الأوضاع خطيرة
I wonder if Luffy and the others are okay.
أتساءل ما إن كان لوفي والبقيّة بخير
Luffy's fine. The one I'm worried about is Nami.
لوفي بخير. أنا قلق على نامي-سان
The town is becoming quite empty.
ولكن أصبحت هذه المدينة فارغة
The wind is gradually getting stronger, too. People have started evacuating.
وتقوى الرياح شيئًا فشيئًا بدأ الناس بالإخلاء
Dammit...
...سحقًا
Hey, Robin!
!روبين-تشان! إلى أين ذهبتِ؟
This scent... Could it be...?
...هذه الرائحة... لا يمكن
Chopper, what's up?!
ما الخطب يا تشوبر؟
Hey, Chopper?!
!تشوبر؟
Hey! Wait!
!أنت! انتظر
She's here.
!إنّها قريبة
Hey, Chopper!
!تشوبر! تشوبر
H-Hey, are you okay?!
!هـ-هل أنت بخير؟
Chopper! Are you okay?!
!تشوبر! هل أنت بخير؟
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
C'mon, don't be so reckless! What the hell is going on?
ويحك، لا تكن متهورًا ...ما خطبك
You ran off so sudden... ly...
...بدأت بالركض... فجأة
– Robin!
!روبين - !روبين-تشان -
Where have you been?! We looked all over for you!
!أ-أين كنتِ؟ بحثنا عنك
Everyone's worried!
!الجميع قلقون هيّا، لنرجع إلى النُزل معًا
A lot's happened since you disappeared. I'll explain everything.
حدثت الكثير من الأمور لنا .سأشرح لك بالتفصيل
But this distance is annoying.
ولكن هذه المسافة مزعجة
Hold on! I'll be right over there!
!تمهلي! سآتي الآن
No, that's okay. Stay there.
لا، لا مشكلة. ابق هناك
I won't be...
لن أعود إليكم
We're parting ways here... in this town.
...سنفترق... هنا في هذه المدينة
Wh-What're you saying, Robin?
مـ-ماذا تقولين يا روبين-تشان؟
Oh, I get it. It's about the newspaper, right?
فهمت. لا بدّ وأنّك تعنين الصحيفة !لا تقلقي حولها
None of us believe it.
لا أحد منّا يصدقها
Pirates are falsely accused all the time!
!واتّهام القراصنة باطلًا هو أمر معتاد
Yeah...
...صحيح
I'm sorry you were all framed for such an outrageous crime.
آسفة لتعرضكم للّوم على جريمة لا مبرر لها
But the article is telling the truth.
ولكن المقالة صحيحة
I really did infiltrate the mayor's residence last night.
أنا من اقتحمت قصر العمدة البارحة بالفعل
No...
...مستحيل
None of you know the darkness I carry within me.
أحملُ في داخلي ظلامًا لا تعرفون عنه شيئًا
This darkness will destroy you someday.
سيدمركم هذا الظلام يومًا
To date, every organization that's brought in Nico Robin has been wiped out.
المنظمات التي كان لها علاقة بنيكو روبين حتّى هذا اليوم
As a matter of fact, I'm pinning this crime on you and planning to run away.
في الحقيقة، أخطط بإلقاء لوم هذه الجريمة عليكم والهروب
The situation will only worsen.
ستسوء الأمور
What do you mean?! Why are you–
...ماذا تعنين؟! لماذا قد
Why I'm doing it... is something you don't need to know.
سبب قيامي لهذا هو شيء لا داعي لأن تعرفونه
Robin! I don't get what you're saying! What happened to you?!
!روبين-تشان! لا أفهم ما تقولين !ما خطبك؟
Robin! Let's go back together!
!روبين! لنرجع معًا
I only spent a short time with you, but after today...
...قضينا فترة قصيرة معًا، ولكن بعد اليوم
I'll never see you again.
لن أراكم ثانية
Thank you for being so kind to someone like me.
شكرًا للطفكم مع شخص مثلي
Farewell.
الوداع
Wait...
...انتظري
Hey... wait...
...لحظة... انتظري
I can't...
...لن
accept this.
أقبل هذا
Hey...
...لحظة
Wait!
!انتظري
Stop joking!
!توقفي عن المزاح
Wait! Robin!
!انتظري! روبين-تشان
Robin!
!روبين-تشان
Wait! Robin! Robin!
!انتظري! روبين-تشان! روبين-تشان
I lost sight of her.
فقدت أثرها
Yeah.
أجل
Chopper...
...تشوبر
Go join Luffy and the others and tell them everything that just happened.
اجتمع بلوفي والبقيّة وأخبرهم ...عن كلّ ما حدث توًّا
Don't leave out a single word.
احرص على ذكر كلّ شيء بالتفصيل
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
We'll part ways here for a bit.
أنا سآخذ طريقًا آخر
Well, don't worry. I won't do anything reckless.
ولكن لا تقلق. لن أفعل شيئًا متهورًا
Where'd they go?
إلى أين ذهبوا؟
Look in every nook and cranny!
!ابحثوا في كلّ مكان
Could they be on the rooftops?!
أيمكن أنّهم تسلقوا سطحًا ما؟
Dammit! We lost 'em!
سحقًا، لقد أضعناهم
But they definitely ran in this direction!
!ولكنّهم هربوا إلى هنا بلا شك
Should we check over there?!
هل نذهب للتحقق هناك؟
And we'll search inside the buildings!
!سنبحث داخل المباني إذًا
Alright! Let's split up and move out!
!حسنًا، لنفترق إلى مجموعتين ونبحث
– Yeah!
!أجل
Is it okay now?
أيكفي؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد
Where did you lose them?!
!أين فقدنا أثرهم؟
A bit longer.
أكثر قليلًا
Please...
...أرجوك
You'll have to come back when I'm not in the middle of evacuating. Now, shoo!
!عد في وقت آخر !سأقوم بالإخلاء الآن. إنّك مزعج
Please... I've got money.
أرجوك... أملك المال
As much lumber, tar, and rope as this will buy...
قدر ما يكفي هذا المال ...من الخشب والطلاء والأحبال
Also, some nails, latches, and tinplates.
...وأيضًا مسامير ومزالج وصفائح
I'm closing the shop.
سأغلق المحل
Ah... I'm sorry, but...
...آسف، ولكن
Okay, then.
حسنًا
But this ain't enough for all that.
ولكن لا تستطيع شراء كلّ ذلك بهذا المال الزهيد
Th-Then, to make up for the rest, I'd like to exchange my tools.
إ-إذًا للتعويض عن الباقي سأبادل بأدواتي
Hey, hey, don't be ridiculous! Stop it!
!لا تكن سخيفًا. توقّف
Cash only! To think you're trying to barter... Are you some kinda rube?
محلّنا يبيع فحسب. كيف فكرت بالمقايضة؟ هل أنت من أهل الريف؟
Okay, fine. You win.
يا إلهي... ما باليد حيلة
H-Hey! Should you be carrying all that stuff with all those injuries?
أ-أنت! هل ستكون بخير بحملك لهذه الأغراض بجروحك؟
Surely you've got friends who can help! Don't you?!
!لا بدّ أنّك تملك رفاقًا، أليس كذلك؟! أنت
See, what did I tell you?
!انظر، أخبرتك
Hey... Wait right there, kiddo!
!تمهّل أيّها الصبي
I'm okay. This is nothing.
أنا بخير. هذا لا شيء
Hey!
!أنت
What is it? Are you gonna help–
...ماذا؟ هل ستساعـ
No...
...لا
Here. Take these.
خذ. خذها. ألست جائعًا؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك
Sure. Be careful on your way back.
أجل... احترس عند عودتك
Be careful on your way back!
!احترس عند عودتك
These're good.
!إنّها لذيذة
These're really good.
إنّها لذيذة حقًا
What a considerate guy...
كان عمًا عطوفًا
The waves are getting pretty high.
بدأت الأمواج ترتفع كثيرًا
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
لا تقلقي. ستكونين بخير
You're a ship that flew in the sky!
!فأنت سفينة حلّقت في السماء
Don't worry!
!لا تقلقي
What's got your bikini in a twist?
ما خطبك فجأة؟
What's wrong, Franky?
ما الخطب يا فرانكي؟
Bro?
أخي؟
I'm getting ticked off!
!بدأت أغضب
Maybe it's about time to go on another rampage!
!حان الوقت لثوران آخر
Bro! Wait for us!
!أخي! انتظرنا
Thanks for the drink, Blueno!
!شكرًا لك على الشراب يا بلونو
What happened to Franky all of a sudden, Miss Kokoro?
ما خطب فرانكي فجأة يا كوكورو-سان؟
Beats me... There's just no telling how idiots think.
لا أدري... لا أعرف ما يفكر به الحمقى
It's finally calmed down.
هدأت الأمور أخيرًا
"Finally calmed down"?!
!هدأت؟
You had all those shipwrights chasing after you!
!لحقنا السفانون أولئك بسببك
You're the one that dragged us into it, too!
!ورطتنا معك
I said it was unavoidable, didn't I?
ألم أخبرك أنّي لم أملك مفرًا من ذلك؟
I'm surprised you figured out where we were, Chopper.
ولكن من المذهل أنّك عرفت مكاننا يا تشوبر
Your scent.
من الرائحة
Ah... Oh, yeah.
صحيح
Right! Wasn't Sanji supposed to be with you?
لحظة... صحيح، أين سانجي؟
Well...
...هذا
Did Robin really say that?!
!أقالت روبين ذلك حقًا؟
Mm-hmm.
نعم
We all knew something was bound to happen, right?
جميعنا كنّا مستعدون لهذا، أليس كذلك؟
Even if it was for a short time, Robin was an enemy before she came aboard.
رغم أنّ ذلك كان لوقت قصير، إلّا أنّا سمحنا لروبين التي واجهناها كعدو، أن تركب سفينتنا
If she suddenly got scared and ran away, it wouldn't sit right with me.
سيكون من المحرج إن هربنا لشعورنا بالخوف
I think it's about time we settled the matter...
...حان الوقت لتسوية هذه المسألة
of whether that woman is friend... or foe.
...ما إن كانت تلك المرأة عدو أم صديق
The situation will only get worse. After today, I'll never see you again.
ستسوء الأمور بعد اليوم... لن أراكم ثانية
You're sure Robin said that, Chopper?
هل أنت متأكد أنّ هذا ما قالته روبين؟
Yeah.
نعم
She said she wouldn't see us after today.
قالت أنّها لن ترانا بعد اليوم
It also sounds like she's planning to do something that could worsen the situation.
يبدو هذا كإعلان منها على أنّها ستفعل شيئًا
Look at how big a fuss the mayor's attempted assassination stirred up.
حدثت كلّ هذه الضجة في المدينة
If it's possible to make the situation worse...
إن كان من الممكن جعل الأمور أسوأ
there's only one thing she can do.
فثمة طريقة واحدة لذلك
Assassinate the mayor for sure this time.
...اغتيال العمدة بالتأكيد هذه المرة
That's the natural conclusion.
هذا هو التفكير الطبيعي
But we know she intends to pin the crime on us,
ولكننا نعرف أنّها تريد أن تلصق تهمة جريمتها بنا عمدًا
so it's possible that it's a trap to lure us to the scene of the crime.
لذا من الممكن أن يكون هذا فخًا لاستدراجنا إلى مسرح الجريمة
A trap?
...فخ
If we're present at the time and place of the assassination,
إن وُجدنا في مكان الاغتيال الذي سيُنفّذ هذه الليلة
the blame will fall to us.
فستُلفّق الجريمة بنا بسهولة
Hey! You make it sound like Robin really is our enemy!
لحظة! تجعل هذا كأنّ !روبين عدوّتنا بالفعل
I'm only saying that it's a possibility.
أتحدث عن الاحتماليّة
I haven't made up my mind yet.
لم أختر أيًّا من الاثنين
Let's say I decide one way or the other right now.
لو كنت قد قررت ما إن كنت سأصدقها أو لا
If the truth ended up being the opposite...
...فلحظة معرفتي أنّ الحقيقة عكس ذلك
it'd slow down my reaction time.
فستبطؤ ردة فعلي
If something's going to happen, it'll be tonight. Are we going?
إن كان سيحدث شيء فسيكون هذه الليلة. هل سنذهب؟
We are.
سنذهب
I don't mind going... but there's a problem.
لا أمانع الذهاب... ولكن توجد مشكلة
Sanji saw Robin walking with someone, right?
رأى سانجي-كن روبين تمشي مع شخص، أليس كذلك؟
Mr. Iceburg said the same thing.
قال أيسبرغ-سان نفس الشيء
She was with someone wearing a mask.
كانت مع شخص يرتدي قناعًا
But it wasn't any of us.
ولكنّه لم يكن أحد منّا
He must be the reason why Robin suddenly changed.
لا بدّ أنّه سبب تغير روبين المفاجئ
Then couldn't it mean he's making Robin do bad things?!
!أليس هو من يجعل روبين تقوم بأمور فظيعة؟
That would be the best case scenario.
سيكون ذلك جيّدًا
The worst case would be if this guy was in cahoots with Robin.
،إن كان صديق روبين الحقيقي فسيكون سيّئًا
But "someone wearing a mask" isn't much of a clue. The mystery is far from solved.
"ولكن "شخص يرتدي قناعًا ليس دليلًا. هذه المشكلة
What's our goal?
ما هي غايتنا؟
We'll capture Robin.
سنمسك بروبين
Otherwise, we'll never find out anything.
لن نعرف شيئًا خلاف ذلك
True. Thinking about it is a waste of time.
بالفعل، سيضيع التفكير وقتنا فحسب
Come to think of it...
...ولكن إلّم تخنّي الذاكرة
the World Government has been trying to capture that woman for twenty years,
كانت حكومة العالم تحاول القبض على تلك المرأة لعشرين سنة
and, somehow, she's remained at large.
ولم يستطيعوا بعد
But if we wanna know the truth, this is the only way.
ولكن لا نملك سوى ذلك الخيار لمعرفة الحقيقة
Okay, I'll do my best too!
!حسنًا، سأبذل جهدي أيضًا
Well then, let's go...
...لنذهب إذًا
to the Galley-La Company!
!إلى شركة غاليلا
Dammit! It's getting dark.
تبًّا! بدأ الظلام يحلّ أخيرًا
Paulie! We've gotta call off the search! The Backstreets will become dangerous soon.
باولي-سان، هذا مستحيل !ستصبح الشوارع الخلفيّة خطرة قريبًا
Yeah, let's go back.
أجل، لنتراجع
I'll be at main office.
سأذهب إلى المقر
Okay!
!مفهوم
Hey, guys! We're going back!
!سنرجع أيّها الجميع
Straw Hat! Show yourself!
!قبعة القش! اخرج
Where're you hiding?!
!أين أنت؟
Straw Hat! That bastard...!
!قبعة القش! ذلك الوغد
I thought the guy had at least a bit of mettle.
بدا لي شجاعًا قليلًا
But he doesn't even show himself.
ولكنّه لا يخرج
But Bro, the entire island is out for their heads.
ولكن يا أخي، جميع من في الجزيرة يكنّون ضغينة عليهم الآن
She's right. I bet they're scurrying around like rats.
صحيح. لا بدّ وأنّهم يهربون من مكان إلى آخر
But is everything okay? What's up with you two?
بالمناسبة، ما خطبكما؟ ماذا تفعلان؟
We're vulnerable to strong winds from the front.
إنّنا ضعيفتان أمام الرياح من الأمام
More importantly, Bro, the way you're raging today is different from usual.
الأهم من ذلك يا أخي غضبك مختلف عن المعتاد اليوم
Letting stuff build up inside isn't like you.
ترك الأمور تتراكم في داخلك ليس لائقًا بك
Gimme a break! That's just what I'm like this week!
!اصمتي! أنا هكذا هذا الأسبوع
Bro!
!أخي
Bro! Did you beat up those bastards?
أخي! هل أبرحت أولئك الأوغاد ضربًا؟
No, not yet.
لا، ليس بعد
There was some crazy interference, so they got away.
واجهنا تدخلًا مزعجًا جدًّا، ولذلك هربوا
They got away from you when you were angry?!
!هربوا منك أثناء غضبك؟
Those are some lucky sons of bitches...
!يملكون حظًّا مذهلًا
I see. I just assumed that you beat up all the others
فهمت... ولكن بما أنّي رأيت طويل الأنف يصلح السفينة وحده
Huh? You found one of them?!
!ماذا؟! أكان أحدهم هناك؟
Y... Yes, on their ship.
نـ-نعم، في السفينة
If you've found one of them, that makes it easy.
إن وجدتم أحدهم، فهذا يجعل الأمور أسهل
We can use him to make 'em reveal themselves!
!سنستغله لاستدراجهم جميعًا
Bro's got his bad-guy face on.
يـ-يظهر أخي وجهه الشرير
Well then, you guys! I want you to start marching through town...
!حسنًا إذًا يا رفاق ...بدءًا من الآن، سيروا خلال المدينة
shouting, "We've got long-nose!
!صارخين "لقد قبضنا على طويل الأنف
To keep him from sleeping with the fishes, come to the warehouse under the bridge!
إن كنت لا تريده أن يغرق في البحر
Franky sends his regards!"
!مع تحيّات فرانكي
I'm gonna go kidnap that long-nose and make it the truth.
ولجعل ذلك حقيقة سأذهب لخطف طويل الأنف
Okay, Bro! Leave it to us!
!مفهوم يا أخي! اترك الأمر لنا
– Aqua Laguna is coming!
!أكوا لاغونا قادمة
We're Aqua Laguna!
!نحن أكوا لاغونا
So what's going on with those assassins?
ماذا حدث مع الجناة إذًا؟
I heard that they haven't been caught yet.
سمعت أنّه لم يُقبض عليهم في نهاية المطاف
How disturbing. Ahh, what a pain...
...هكذا إذًا. هذا مزعج
I heard they might attack again tonight in the confusion of the storm.
يقال أنّهم قد يشنون هجومًا ثانيًا هذه الليلة في خضم هوشة العاصفة
Aqua Laguna is here!
!وصلت أكوا لاغونا
But it'll be crazy tonight.
ولكن ستكون هذه الليلة مذهلة
I heard all the craftsmen will be guarding the main office.
سمعت أنّ جميع حرفيي غاليلا سيحمون المكتب الرئيسي
Whoa! That's pretty serious!
!هذا خطير
How many are there in the Straw Hat Pirates?
كم عدد طاقم قراصنة قبعة القش أصلًا؟
Some say fifty... others say it's closer to a hundred.
يقول البعض 50. ويقول البعض 100
The captain's got a 100-million bounty after all.
فيملك القبطان 100 مليون على رأسه في نهاية المطاف
Some said that 3,000 of his men would advance from the sea!
يقولون أنّ 3000 من رجاله !سيأتون من البحر
That sounds totally dangerous!
!يبدو هذا خطيرًا جدًّا
Galley-La Company! Form a line, and don't leave any openings!
!شكّلوا صفًّا ولا تتركوا أيّ فراغ يا شركة غاليلا
– Yeah!
!نعم
Don't allow even a single rat inside!
!لا تسمحوا حتّى لفأر بالدخول
Bring it on!
!هلموا
Shut up! Be quiet, Tilestone!
!اصمت! كن هادئًا يا تايلستون
I was told they weren't on the sea train.
سمعت أنّهم لم يكونوا على متن القطار البحري
Then they're still somewhere on the island, huh?
ذلك يعني أنّهم لا يزالون في مكان ما من هذه الجزيرة، أليس كذلك؟
But they're fools if they really appear with all these guards around.
ولكنّهم سيكونون حمقى إن أتوا بوجود كل هذه الحراسة
I heard that an idiot plunged in here in the middle of the day today.
سمعت أنّ أحمق اقتحم هذا المكان في منتصف النهار اليوم
Common sense doesn't apply to them.
لا تفكّر بمنطقيّة
they don't have to go this far.
لا داعي لأن يقوموا بكلّ هذا
They're doing it voluntarily.
إنّهم يفعلون هذا طوعًا
It's like I'm a king.
يعاملونني كملك
By the way, why did you put up Nico Robin's wanted poster in your room?
بالمناسبة، لماذا وضعت ملصق طلب نيكو روبين للعدالة في غرفتك؟
Curious?
أيثير ذلك فضولك؟
A little.
قليلًا
It's better if you don't know.
من الأفضل ألّا تعرفي
She is... a devil.
إنّها... شيطان
There're so many guards in place...
عدد كبير من الأشخاص يحمون المكان
It's a little far.
إنّه بعيد قليلًا
You'll stretch your arm and fly right in, but only after the commotion starts, got it?
ألا تستطيع مدّ يديك والطيران إلى هناك فحسب؟
Yeah. If we start the commotion before they do, then they'll have the advantage.
صحيح. إن سببنا فوضى قبلهم فسيستغلونها لصالحهم فحسب
Listen up!
!اسمعوا
Don't miss even the slightest movement!
!لا تفلتوا أيّ تحرك مهما كان
– Yeah!
!نعم
Innkeeper
صاحب النُزُل
Shipyard Basement Storeroom (Evacuation Center)
مخزن في الطابق السفلي لحوض السفانة (مركز الإخلاء)
Outside Iceburg's Bedroom
خارج غرفة نوم أيسبرغ
Bedroom
غرفة النوم